Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part One
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Files, 1710-1955; 21.07; (65 boxes)
  - Brown, Joseph, 1784-1868, 1857 (Box 11, Folder 338)
  - Browne, Edward Harold, 1811-1891, 1867-88, undated (Box 11, Folder 339-343)
  - Browne, G.F. (George Forrest), 1833- 1930, 1895-1907 (Box 11, Folder 344-347)
  - Bruce, J. Collingwood (John Collingwood), 1805-1892, 1864 (Box 12, Folder 348)
  - Bryan, Alfred, 1852-1899, 1880-89 (Box 12, Folder 349)
  - Bryce, James Bryce, Viscount, 1838- 1922, 1893-1918 (Box 12, Folder 350-351)
  - Buccleuch, Charlotte Anne (Thynne) Montagu-Douglas-Scott, Duchess of, 1811-1895, undated (Box 12, Folder 352)
  - Buchanan, Robert Williams, 1841-1901, 1871-90, undated (Box 12, Folder 353-354)
  - Buckingham and Chandos, Richard Plantagenet Campbell Temple Nugent Brydges Chandros Grenville, Duke of, 1823-1889, 1862-88, undated (Box 12, Folder 355-358)
  - Buckingham and Chandos, Richard Plantagenet Temple Nugent Brydges Chandos Grenville, Duke of, 1797-1861, 1849, undated (Box 12, Folder 359-360)
  - Buckingham, James Silk, 1786-1855, 1854 (Box 12, Folder 361)
  - Buckland, Francis T. (Francis Trevelyan), 1826-1880, undated (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - Buckland, William, 1784-1856, undated (Box 12, Folder 363-364)
  - Buckle, George Earle, 1854-1935, 1894-1904 (Box 12, Folder 365-366)
  - Buckley, Arabella B. (Arabella Burton), 1840-1929, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 367)
  - Buckman, James, 1816-1884, 1861-62 (Box 12, Folder 368)
  - Buckstone, John Baldwin, 1802-1879, 1866-73, undated (Box 12, Folder 369-370)
  - Bullen, George, 1816-1894, 1862 (Box 12, Folder 371)
  - Bulwer, Henry, Sir, 1801-1872
    See: Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, box 20, folder 684
  - Burdett, Francis, Sir, 1770-1844, 1827-30, undated (Box 13, Folder 372-373)
  - Burdett-Couts, Angela Georgina Burdett-Couts, Baroness, 1814-1906, 1854-86 (Box 13, Folder 374-377)
  - Burgon, John William, 1813-1888, 1861-87 (Box 13, Folder 378-381)
  - Burgoyne, John F. (John Fox), Sir, 1782-1871, 1861-71 (Box 13, Folder 382-383)
  - Burgoyne, John Montagu, Sir, Bart., 1832-1921, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 384)
  - Burnard, F.C. (Francis Cowley), Sir, 1836-1917, 1880-91, undated (Box 13, Folder 385-386)
  - Burns, John, 1858-1943, 1892-1920, undated (Box 13, Folder 387-396)
  - Burnside, Helen Marion, 1844-1923, undated (Box 13, Folder 397)
  - Burt, Thomas, 1837-1922, 1874-98 (Box 13, Folder 398-399)
  - Burton, Isabel, Lady, 1831-1896, 1894 (Box 13, Folder 400)
  - Bury, Chalotte Campbell, Lady, 1775- 1861, 1837, undated (Box 13, Folder 401-402)
  - Butler, Arthur G. (Arthur Gardiner), 1844-1925, 1883-91, undated (Box 13, Folder 403-404)
  - Butler, Elizabeth, Lady, 1846-1933, undated (Box 13, Folder 405)
  - Butt, Isaac, 1813-1879, undated (Box 13, Folder 406)
  - Byles, John Barnard, Sir, 1801-1884, undated (Box 13, Folder 407-408)
  - Byng, Francis E. G., 1882 (Box 13, Folder 409)
  - Byron, George Anson Byron, Baron, 1789-1868, 1809-29 (Box 13, Folder 410-411)
  - Byron, Henry J., 1863 Jun 27 (Box 13, Folder 410-411)
  - Cadogan, Beatrix Jane (Craven) Cadogan, Countess, 1844-1907, undated (Box 14, Folder 412)
  - Cadogan, Henry Charles Cadogan, Earl, 1812-1873, 1847 (Box 14, Folder 413-414)
  - Cadogan, Henry Charles Cadogan, Earl, 1812-1873, 1863-69 (Box 14, Folder 415)
  - Caine, Hall, Sir, 1853-1931, undated (Box 14, Folder 416)
  - Caine, W. S. (William Sproston), 1842- 1903, 1892-1901, undated (Box 14, Folder 417-419)
  - Cairns, Hugh McCalmont Cairns, Earl, 1819-1885, 1859-87, undated (Box 14, Folder 420-425)
  - Callcott, Augustus Wall, Sir, 1779- 1844, undated (Box 14, Folder 426)
  - Calmour, Afred C. (Alfred Cecil), 1857?-1912, 1898 (Box 14, Folder 427)
  - Call, William Pratt, Sir, Bart., 1781- 1851, 1842 (Box 14, Folder 428)
  - Calvert, Charles Alexander, 1828-1879, undated (Box 14, Folder 429)
  - Cambridge, George William Frederick Charles, Duke of, 1819-1904, 1858-94 (Box 14, Folder 430-435)
  - Cambert, George Charles Pratt, Marquess, 1799-1866, 1841-60 (Box 14, Folder 436-437)
  - Cameron, C. H. (Charles Hay), 1795-1880, undated (Box 14, Folder 438)
  - Cameron, G. Poulett (George Poulett), 1805-1882, 1876-77, undated (Box 14, Folder 439-440)
  - Camoys, Thomas Stonor, Baron, 1797- 1881, 1868 (Box 14, Folder 441)
  - Campbell, John Campbell, Baron, 1779- 1861, 1835-60, undated (Box 14, Folder 442-446)
  - Camps, William, 1844 (Box 14, Folder 447)
  - Canning, George, 1770-1827, undated (Box 14, Folder 448)
  - Canterbury, Charles Manners-Sutton, Viscount, 1780-1845, 1819-45 (Box 14, Folder 449-453)
  - Capei, Thomas John, 1836-1911, 1880 (Box 14, Folder 454)
  - Capel-Cure, Edward, d. 1890, 1876-90 (Box 14, Folder 455)
  - Cardigan, James Thomas Brudenell, Earl of, 1797-1868, undated (Box 14, Folder 456)
  - Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, 1849-78, undated (Box 14, Folder 457-460)
  - Carew, Reginald Pole, Sir, 1849-1924, 1900 (Box 14, Folder 461)
  - Carlingford, Chichester Samuel Parkinson-Fortescue, Baron, 1823-1898, 1879, undated (Box 14, Folder 462)
  - Carlisle, Anthony, Sir, 1768-1840, 1838 (Box 14, Folder 463)
  - Carlisle, George William Frederick Howard, Earl of, 1802-1864, 1849, undated (Box 14, Folder 464-466)
  - Carlos, Edward John, 1798-1851, 1837 (Box 14, Folder 467)
  - Carnarvon, Henry Howard Molyneux, Earl of, 1831-1890, 1862-77, undated (Box 14, Folder 468-472)
  - Carpenter, Edward, 1844-1929, undated (Box 14, Folder 473)
  - Carr, Alice Vansittart Strettel, 1850-, undated (Box 14, Folder 474)
  - Carreño, Teresa, 1853-1917, 1902 (Box 14, Folder 475)
  - Carrington, Charlotte Augusta Annabella (Drummond-Burrell) Carrington, Baroness, 1815-1879, undated (Box 14, Folder 476)
  - Carrington, Robert John Carrington, Baron, 1796-1868, 1862 (Box 14, Folder 477)
  - Carte, Richard D'Oyley, 1844-1901, 1878-84 (Box 14, Folder 478)
  - Carrodus, John Tiplady, 1836-1895, 1876-82 (Box 14, Folder 479)
  - Carter, Thomas Thellusson, 1808-1901, undated (Box 14, Folder 480)
  - Cartwright, Charles, 1894, undated (Box 14, Folder 481)
  - Cartwright, William Cornwallis, 1826- 1915, undated (Box 14, Folder 482)
  - Caryll, Dolly, 1891 (Box 14, Folder 483)
  - Carysfort, William Proby, Earl of, 1836-1909, 1879 (Box 14, Folder 484)
  - Cavagnari, Pierre Louis Napoleon, Sir, 1841-1879, undated (Box 15, Folder 485)
  - Cave, B, 1865 (Box 15, Folder 486)
  - Cave, Lewis W. (Lewis William), 1832- 1897, 1887, undated (Box 15, Folder 487)
  - Cave, Stephen, 1820-1880, undated (Box 15, Folder 488)
  - Cavendish, Ada, 1839-1895, 1882, undated (Box 15, Folder 489)
  - Cavendish, Edward, Lord, 1838-1891, 1850-81 (Box 15, Folder 490)
  - Cayley, Arthur, 1821-1895, undated (Box 15, Folder 491)
  - Cecil, William, Lord, 1854-1943, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 492)
  - Cecil of Chelwood, Robert Gascoyne- Cecil, Viscount, 1864-1958, 1887 (Box 15, Folder 493)
  - Chaffers, William, 1811-1892, 1872 (Box 15, Folder 494)
  - Challis, James, 1803-1882, 1849 (Box 15, Folder 495)
  - Chalmers, Thomas, 1780-1847, 1835-38, undated (Box 15, Folder 496)
  - Chamberlain, Neville Bowles, Sir, 1820-1902, 1888 (Box 15, Folder 497)
  - Chambers, Robert, 1802-1871, undated (Box 15, Folder 498)
  - Chambers, Thomas, Sir, 1814-1891, 1885 (Box 15, Folder 499)
  - Chant, Laura Ormiston, 1848-1923, 1888, undated (Box 15, Folder 500)
  - Chaplin, Henry Chaplin, Viscount, 1841-1923, 1883-1913, undated (Box 15, Folder 501)
  - Chapman, J., Bishop of Colombo, undated (Box 15, Folder 502)
  - Charles, Arthur, Sir, 1839-1921, 1892-1905, undated (Box 15, Folder 503)
  - Charles, Elizabeth Rundle, 1828-1896, undated (Box 15, Folder 504)
  - Charlesworth, Edward, 1844 (Box 15, Folder 505)
  - Charlesworth, Maria Louisa, 1819-1880, undated (Box 15, Folder 506)
  - Charlotte Augusta Matilda, Queen Consort of Friedrich I, King of Württemberg, 1766-1828, undated (Box 15, Folder 507)
  - Charlotte Elizabeth, 1790-1846
    See: Tonna, Charlotte Elizabeth, 1790-1846, box 59, folder 2159
  - Charlton, Basil, 1897 (Box 15, Folder 508)
  - Chelmsford, Frederic Augustus Thesiger, Baron, 1827-1905, 1900, undated (Box 15, Folder 509)
  - Chelmsford, Frederic Thesiger, Baron, 1794-1878, 1838-70, undated (Box 15, Folder 510)
  - Chenery, Thomas, 1826-1884, 1879, undated (Box 15, Folder 511)
  - Chesham, Charles Compton William Cavendish, Baron, 1850-1907, 1889 (Box 15, Folder 512)
  - Chesham, Henrietta Frances (Lascelles) Cavendish, Baroness, 1830-1884, undated (Box 15, Folder 513)
  - Chesney, Francis Rawdon, 1789-1872, 1840-43 (Box 15, Folder 514)
  - Chesney, George Tomkyns, 1830-1895, 1877 (Box 15, Folder 515)
  - Chesterfield, George Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1866, 1841, undated (Box 15, Folder 516)
  - Chetwode, Elizabeth (Evans), d. 1894, undated (Box 15, Folder 517)
  - Chetwynd, George, Sir, 1849-1917, undated (Box 15, Folder 518)
  - Chevalier, Albert, 1861-1923, 1891-98, undated (Box 15, Folder 519)
  - Chewton, William Frederick Waldegrave, Viscount, 1816-1854
    See: Waldegrave, William Frederick, styled Viscount Chewton, 1816-1854, box 61, folder 2214
  - Cheyne, Thomas Kelley, 1841-1915, 1887-1900, undated (Box 15, Folder 520)
  - Chichester, Henry Thomas Pelham, Earl of, 1804-1886, 1854-86, undated (Box 16, Folder 521)
  - Chilton, Aretas Akers-Douglas, Viscount, 1851-1926, undated (Box 16, Folder 522)
  - Chipp, Edmund Thomas, 1823-1886, 1879 (Box 16, Folder 523)
  - Chitty, Joseph William, Sir, 1828-1899, 1887 (Box 16, Folder 524)
  - Cholmondeley, George Horatio Cholmondeley, Marquis of, 1792-1870, 1862, undated (Box 16, Folder 525)
  - Chrichton-Browne, James, Sir, 1840-1938, 1890 (Box 16, Folder 526-527)
  - Christian, Prince of Schleswig- Holstein, 1831-1917, 1876-98, undated (Box 16, Folder 528)
  - Christian Victor, Prince of Schleswig- Holstein, 1867-1900, 1895-97 (Box 16, Folder 529-530)
  - Christie, Albany J., undated (Box 16, Folder 531)
  - Church, A. H. (Arthur Herbert), 1834- 1915, 1896 (Box 16, Folder 532)
  - Church, R. W. (Richard William), 1815- 1890, 1872-90, undated (Box 16, Folder 533)
  - Churchill, Alfred, Lord, 1824-1893, 1889 (Box 16, Folder 534)
  - Churchill, Randolph Henry Spencer, Lord, 1849-1895, undated (Box 16, Folder 535)
  - Churchill, Randolph Spencer, Lady, 1854-1921, 1886, undated (Box 16, Folder 536)
  - Churchill, Winston, Sir, 1874-1965, 1935, undated (Box 16, Folder 537)
  - Churston, John Yarde-Buller, Baron, 1846-1910, undated (Box 16, Folder 538)
  - City of London, Sewer Rate, 1845 (Box 16, Folder 539)
  - Clanricarde, Ulick de Burgh, Marquis of, 1802-1874, 1852 (Box 16, Folder 540)
  - Clarendon, Edward Hyde Villiers, Earl of, 1846-1915, 1869-1904 (Box 16, Folder 541)
  - Clarendon, George Herbert Hyde William, Earl of, 1877-1955, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 542)
  - Clarendon, George William Frederick Villiers, Earl of, 1800-1870, 1853-65, undated (Box 16, Folder 543)
  - Clarendon, Katherine (Grimston) Barham Villiers, Countess, 1810-1874, 1840 (Box 16, Folder 544)
  - Clark, Andrew, Sir, Bart., M.D., 1826-1893, 1890-92, undated (Box 16, Folder 545)
  - Clark, James, Sir, 1788-1870, 1843-69, undated (Box 16, Folder 546-547)
  - Clark, Richard, 1780-1856, 1837 (Box 16, Folder 548)
  - Clarke, Edward George, Sir, 1841-1931, 1888-1931, undated (Box 16, Folder 549)
  - Clarkson, Willy, b. 1861, undated (Box 16, Folder 550)
  - Claxton, Adelaide, fl. 1860-1876, undated (Box 16, Folder 551)
  - Clay, Frederic, 1838-1889, undated (Box 16, Folder 552)
  - Clay, James, 1804 or 5-1873, undated (Box 16, Folder 553)
  - Clay, William, Sir, 1791-1867, 1832-57 (Box 16, Folder 554)
  - Clayden, Arthur William, 1855-1944, 1899 (Box 16, Folder 555)
  - Clayton, John, 1843-1888, 1880, undated (Box 16, Folder 556)
  - Clerk, George, Sir, 1787-1867, 1819, undated (Box 16, Folder 557)
  - Cleveland, Elizabeth (Russell) Vane, Duchess of, 1777-1861, 1839 (Box 16, Folder 558)
  - Cleveland, Henry Vane, Duke of, 1788- 1864, 1827-59 (Box 16, Folder 559)
  - Cleveland, William Harry Vane, Duke of, 1766-1842, 1832-36, undated (Box 16, Folder 560)
  - Clifford, John, 1836-1923, 1887-1906 (Box 16, Folder 561)
  - Clifford, W. K., Mrs. d. 1929, undated (Box 16, Folder 562)
  - Clifton, Robert Bellamy, 1836-1921, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 563)
  - Clinton, Charles John Fynes, 1799-1872, undated (Box 16, Folder 564)
  - Clough, Anne Jemima, 1820-1892, undated (Box 16, Folder 565)
  - Cobbe, Francis Power, 1822-1903, 1865 (Box 16, Folder 566)
  - Cobden, Richard, 1804-1865, 1863, undated (Box 16, Folder 567)
  - Coborn, Charles, 1852-1945, 1887, undated (Box 16, Folder 568)
  - Cockburn, Alexander James Edmund, Sir, 1802-1880, 1852-74, undated (Box 16, Folder 569)
  - Cockburn, Henry Cockburn, Lord, 1779- 1854, 1845, undated (Box 16, Folder 570)
  - Coffin, Charles Hayden, 1862-1935, 1896-1900, undated (Box 16, Folder 571)
  - Coghill, J. Sinclair, 1899 (Box 16, Folder 572)
  - Coghlan, Charles F., 1841-1899, undated (Box 16, Folder 573)
  - Coit, Stanton, 1857-1944, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 574)
  - Coke, Charlotte (Talbot), 1843-1922, undated (Box 17, Folder 575)
  - Coke, Thomas William, Earl of Leicester, 1752-1842, undated (Box 17, Folder 576)
  - Colborne, Nicholas William Ridley- Colborne, Baron, 1779-1854, undated (Box 17, Folder 577)
  - Colchester, Charles Abbot, Baron, 1789-1867, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 578)
  - Cole, Grenville A.J. (Grenville Arthur James), 1859-1924, 1899 (Box 17, Folder 579)
  - Cole, Horace de Vere, undated (Box 17, Folder 580)
  - Coleridge, Bernard Coleridge, Baron, 1851-1927, 1885-1905 (Box 17, Folder 581)
  - Coleridge, Gilbert James Duke, b. 1859, 1899-1919 (Box 17, Folder 582)
  - Coleridge, John Duke Coleridge, Baron, 1820-1894, 1840-92, undated (Box 17, Folder 583-584)
  - Coleridge, John Taylor, Sir, 1790-1876, 1835, undated (Box 17, Folder 585)
  - Coleridge, William Hart, 1789-1849, undated (Box 17, Folder 586)
  - Coles, Vincent Stuckey Stratton, 1845- 1929, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 587)
  - Collette, Charles, 1842-1924, 1892, undated (Box 17, Folder 588)
  - Collingwood, Cuthbert, 1826-1908, 1872 (Box 17, Folder 589)
  - Collins, Arthur Pelham, 1863-1932, 1900-09, undated (Box 17, Folder 590)
  - Collins, Mabel, 1851-1927, undated (Box 17, Folder 591)
  - Collmann, Leonard, 1897 (Box 17, Folder 592)
  - Colville, Charles John Colville, Viscount, 1818-1903, 1874, undated (Box 17, Folder 593)
  - Colville, William James, 1827-1903, 1881 (Box 17, Folder 594)
  - Colvin, Sidney, Sir, 1845-1927, undated (Box 17, Folder 595)
  - Combermere, Stapleton Cotton, Viscount, 1773-1865, 1833 (Box 17, Folder 596)
  - Compton, Edward, 1854-1918, undated (Box 17, Folder 597)
  - Compton, Edward, Mrs., undated (Box 17, Folder 598)
  - Compton, Henry, 1805-1877, 1862-64, undated (Box 17, Folder 599)
  - Conant, H. C. (Hannah Chaplin), 1809- 1865, 1861 (Box 17, Folder 600)
  - Conington, John, 1825-1869, undated (Box 17, Folder 601)
  - Connaught, Louise Margarethe Alexandra Victoria Agnes, Duchess of, 1860-1917, undated (Box 17, Folder 602)
  - Connor, George Henry, 1822-1883, 1882 (Box 17, Folder 603)
  - Conquest, George, 1837-1901, undated (Box 17, Folder 604)
  - Conroy, John, Sir, Bart., 1786-1854, 1884-88, undated (Box 17, Folder 605)
  - Conway, Harry H., undated (Box 17, Folder 606)
  - Conybeare, F. C. (Frederick Cornwallis), 1856-1924, 1898 (Box 17, Folder 607)
  - Conybeare, William John, 1815-1857, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 608)
  - Conyngham, Henry Conyngham, Marquess, 1766-1832, undated (Box 17, Folder 609)
  - Cooke, T. P. (Thomas Potter), 1786-1864, 1829-56 (Box 18, Folder 610)
  - Cooper, Alfred, Sir, 1838-1908, 1890 (Box 18, Folder 611)
  - Cooper, Arthur Nevile, b. 1850, 1901 (Box 18, Folder 612)
  - Cooper, Astley, Sir, 1768-1841, undated (Box 18, Folder 613)
  - Cooper, Charles Henry, 1808-1866, 1843 (Box 18, Folder 614)
  - Cooper, George Armytype, 1859 (Box 18, Folder 615)
  - Cooper, John, fl. 1810-1870, 1833 (Box 18, Folder 616)
  - Cooper, Samuel, 1780-1848, 1844 (Box 18, Folder 617)
  - Cope, Arthur Stockdale, Sir, 1857-1940, 1898-1917 (Box 18, Folder 618)
  - Copeland, William Taylor, 1797-1868, 1860 (Box 18, Folder 619)
  - Coquelin, Constant, 1841-1909, 1902, undated (Box 18, Folder 620)
  - Corbould, Edward Henry, 1815-1905, 1884, undated (Box 18, Folder 621)
  - Corelli, Marie, 1855-1924, 1891-1912, undated (Box 18, Folder 622)
  - Cork, Richard Edmund St. Lawrence Boyle, Earl of, 1829-1904, undated (Box 18, Folder 623)
  - Corrie, George Elwes, 1793-1885, 1827-37 (Box 18, Folder 624)
  - Corry, Henry Thomas Lowry, 1803-1873, 1868 (Box 18, Folder 625)
  - Cottenham, Charles Christopher Pepys, Earl of, 1781-1851, 1834-39, undated (Box 18, Folder 626)
  - Cotterill, Henry, 1812-1886, 1860-74 (Box 18, Folder 627)
  - Cottesloe, Thomas Francis Fremantle, Baron, 1830-1918, 1885 (Box 18, Folder 628)
  - Cotton, R. L. (Richard Lynch), 1794- 1880, undated (Box 18, Folder 629)
  - Couch, Richard Quiller-, 1816-1863, 1856 (Box 18, Folder 630)
  - Courtenay, C. C., 1872 (Box 18, Folder 631)
  - Courtenay, Thomas Peregrine, 1782-1841, 1815 (Box 18, Folder 632)
  - Courtneidge, Robert, b. 1859, 1915 (Box 18, Folder 633)
  - Courtney, Catherine (Potter), d. 1929, 1890-98, undated (Box 18, Folder 634)
  - Cousins, Samuel, 1801-1887, undated (Box 18, Folder 635)
  - Coventry, George William Coventry, Earl of, 1838-1930, 1878-1905 (Box 18, Folder 636)
  - Cowell, Edward B. (Edward Byles), 1826-1903, 1870-98 (Box 18, Folder 637)
  - Cowell, John Clayton, Sir, 1887 (Box 18, Folder 638)
  - Cowen, Joseph, Sir, 1800-1873, 1828-83, undated (Box 18, Folder 639)
  - Cowen, Joseph, 1831-1900, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 640)
  - Cox, George W. (George William), 1827- 1902, 1892 (Box 18, Folder 641)
  - Coxe, Seymour Richard, 1842-1922, 1888 (Box 18, Folder 642)
  - Coyne, J. Stirling (Joseph Stirling), 1803-1868, 1865 (Box 18, Folder 643)
  - Cozens-Hardy, Herbert Hardy Cozens-Hardy, Baron, 1838-1920, 1900-07 (Box 18, Folder 644)
  - Crabb, Louisa, undated (Box 19, Folder 645)
  - Craik, Dinah Maria Mulock, 1826-1887, undated (Box 19, Folder 646)
  - Cranbrook, Gathorne Gathorne-Hardy, Earl of, 1814-1906, 1842-1901, undated (Box 19, Folder 647)
  - Crane, Walter, 1845-1915, 1878-1914, undated (Box 19, Folder 648)
  - Cranworth, Robert Monsey Rolfe, Baron, 1790-1868, 1853-64 (Box 19, Folder 649)
  - Crawford, F. Marion (Francis Marion), 1854-1909, undated (Box 19, Folder 650)
  - Crawford, Robert Fitzgerald Copland, 1885 (Box 19, Folder 651)
  - Crawford, Thomas, Sir, b. 1824, 1890 (Box 19, Folder 652)
  - Crease, John Frederick (?), Major-Gen. Sir, d. 1907, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 653)
  - Creighton, Louise von Glehn, 1850-1936, 1907-09, undated (Box 19, Folder 654)
  - Creighton, M. (Mandell), 1843-1901, 1893-95 (Box 19, Folder 655)
  - Creswick, William, 1813-1888, 1877-82, undated (Box 19, Folder 656)
  - Crewe, Hungerford Crewe, Baron, 1812- 1893, 1878 (Box 19, Folder 657)
  - Crichton, George Arthur Charles, Sir, 1874-1952, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 658)
  - Critchett, George Anderson, Sir, Bart., d. 1925, 1881-1908, undated (Box 19, Folder 659)
  - Croft, Henry Page, 1881-1947, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 660)
  - Croft, John, Sir, 1833-1905, undated (Box 19, Folder 661)
  - Cross, Richard Assheton, 1823-1914, 1858-90, undated (Box 19, Folder 662)
  - Cruikshank, George, 1792-1878, 1868-73, undated (Box 19, Folder 663)
  - Cubitt, Maria, undated (Box 19, Folder 664)
  - Cubitt, William, 1791-1863, undated (Box 19, Folder 665)
  - Cumberland, J., 1836 (Box 19, Folder 666)
  - Cumming, John, 1807-1881, 1847 (Box 19, Folder 667)
  - Cummings, Richard, 1838 (Box 19, Folder 668)
  - Cuney, Frederick, 1819-1881, 1857 (Box 19, Folder 669)
  - Cunningham, Peter, 1816-1869, 1849, undated (Box 19, Folder 670)
  - Cureton, William 1808-1864, 1861-63 (Box 19, Folder 671)
  - Currie, Philip Henry Wodehouse, Sir, 1834-1906, undated (Box 19, Folder 672)
  - Curzon, Frank, 1868-1927, 1900, undated (Box 19, Folder 673)
  - Curzon, George Nathaniel Curzon, Marquis of, 1859-1925, 1900-11, undated (Box 19, Folder 674)
  - Cust, Charles Leopold, Sir, Bart., 1864-1931, 1899-1923, undated (Box 19, Folder 675)
  - Cust, Henry, 1780-1861, undated (Box 19, Folder 676)
  - Cutler, Kate, b. 1870, 1895, undated (Box 19, Folder 677)
  - Cuyler, Theodore L. (Theodore Ledyard), 1822-1909, 1872 (Box 19, Folder 678)
  - Dacre, Amy, undated (Box 20, Folder 679)
  - Dakins, W. H., 1840 (Box 20, Folder 680)
  - Dalby, John, 1860 (Box 20, Folder 681)
  - Dale, Thomas, 1797-1870, 1852 (Box 20, Folder 682)
  - Dalhousie, James Andrew Broun Ramsay, Marquis of, 1812-1860, 1845 (Box 20, Folder 683)
  - Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, 1837-64, undated (Box 20, Folder 684)
  - D'Alroy, Evelyn, 1909, undated (Box 20, Folder 685)
  - Dalton, John Neale, 1839-1931, 1910 (Box 20, Folder 686)
  - Daly, Arnold, 1875-1927, 1901, undated (Box 20, Folder 687)
  - Dana, Henry, b. 1855, 1893-1902 (Box 20, Folder 688)
  - Dance, Charles, 1794-1863, 1858 (Box 20, Folder 689)
  - Danell, James, Bp. of Southwark, 1821- 1881, 1870 (Box 20, Folder 690)
  - D'Appleton and Co., 1871 (Box 20, Folder 691)
  - Darling, Grace Horsley, 1815-1842, undated (Box 20, Folder 692)
  - Darnley, Harriet Mary (Pelham) Bligh, Countess of, 1829-1905, 1881 (Box 20, Folder 693)
  - Darnley, John Stuart Bligh, Earl of, 1827-1896, 1857-75 (Box 20, Folder 694)
  - Dartmouth, William Walter Legge, Earl of, 1823-1891, 1864 (Box 20, Folder 695)
  - Daubeney, Henry Charles Barnston, Sir, 1810-1903, 1850 (Box 20, Folder 696)
  - D'Auberval, Mr., undated (Box 20, Folder 697)
  - Davey, Horace Davey, Baron, 1833-1907, 1887-95, undated (Box 20, Folder 698)
  - Davidson, Randall Thomas, 1848-1930, 1893-1919 (Box 20, Folder 699)
  - Davies, J. Llewelyn (John Llewelyn), 1826-1916, 1903 (Box 20, Folder 700)
  - Davy, Jane (Kerr) Apreece, Lady, 1780- 1855, 1819 (Box 20, Folder 701)
  - Davys, George, 1780-1864, 1845-62, undated (Box 20, Folder 702)
  - Dawson, Bertrand Edward Dawson, Viscount, 1864-1945, 1909-1925 (Box 20, Folder 703)
  - Dawson, Forbes, b. 1860, undated (Box 20, Folder 704)
  - Dawson, Frederick, 1868-1940, 1907 (Box 20, Folder 705)
  - Day, John C. F. S. (John Charles Frederic Sigismund), Sir, 1826-1908, undated (Box 20, Folder 706)
  - Deland, Margaret Wade Campbell, 1857- 1945, 1888 (Box 20, Folder 707)
  - Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879, 1865, undated (Box 20, Folder 708)
  - de la Poer-Beresford, Lilian Warren (Price) Hammersley Spencer-Churchill, d. 1907
    See: Marlborough, Lilian Warren Hammersley Spencer-Churchill, Duchess of, d. 1907, box 40, folder 1429
  - De La Warr, George John Sackville- West, Earl, 1791-1869, 1842-45, undated (Box 20, Folder 709)
  - De La Warr, George Gilbert Reginald Sackville, Earl, 1869-1915, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 710)
  - De L'Isle and Dudley, Mary (Foulis) Sidney, Baroness, 1826-1891, undated (Box 20, Folder 711)
  - De L'Isle and Dudley, Philip Sidney, Baron, 1828-1898, 1873-80 (Box 20, Folder 712)
  - De Mauley, Charles Frederick Ashley Cooper Ponsonby, Baron, 1815-1896, undated (Box 20, Folder 713)
  - De Mauley, Maurice John George Ponsonby, Baron, 1846-1945, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 714)
  - De Mauley, William Francis Spencer Ponsonby, Baron, 1787-1855, 1846 (Box 20, Folder 715)
  - De Morgan, Augustus, 1806-1871, 1870 (Box 20, Folder 716)
  - Denby, William Basil Percy Fielding, Earl of, 1796-1865, 1840 (Box 20, Folder 717)
  - Denison, Edward, 1801-1854, 1841-50 (Box 20, Folder 718)
  - Denison, George Anthony, 1805-1896, 1855-95, undated (Box 20, Folder 719)
  - Denison, W. J. (William Joseph), 1770- 1849, 1828 (Box 20, Folder 720)
  - Denman, George, 1819-1896, 1882-92, undated (Box 20, Folder 721)
  - Denman, Thomas Denman, Baron, 1779- 1854, 1831-59 (Box 20, Folder 722)
  - De Ramsey, William Henry Fellowes, Baron, 1848-1925, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 723)